So friends, the scary prank we planned was
successful
[sound of clearing throat].  Now let's
celebrate with cake.  Let's cut the cake shake.
Happy birthday to you brother.  Brother's
Birthday Brother's Birthday   I am
giving you the cake.  I am giving it.   I am making the
cake right now.  Just sit there.  Ok
?
Cake.   I will
place the cake in the outer room.  Then
you come.  Ok?  My dear sister.   The
cake is ready for you.  Please
take the trouble to come out to the front room.   Come on
my tension.
Now we have to catch him and bring him here.   Bring it with your
eyes closed.  Then I,
hey, I am taking you only to the room outside the cake,
close one eye, name it,
come
brother, don't scare me with the birthday girl, so
friends, as today is a
very nice birthday of my dear sister, I have left no stone unturned
in her birthday and do
n't open your eyes right now, the
cake of her birthday girl is ready friends, it is very
beautiful and don't open her eyes right now, bring her, make her sit
comfortably on the sofa, okay
brother, I am making her
sit 100 times.   It
's his hand, friend.
Hey, sit down, it's such a nice cake, we'll
laugh.  Don't open his eyes now, he's fine.
Ok.
Yes, open your eyes for this.  Three to one.
[laughter]
[applause]
How did you like your cake?